really pathetic uncle pathetic pathetic pathetic
de verdad patético tío patético patético
look I just came from
patético mira que justo vengo ahora de
Huelva there's a pizzeria that I
huelva que hay una pizzería que me
love living now come back from
encanta viviendo ahora devuelva de
eating a family pizza that he stuck
comerme una pizza familiar que me metió
here between my chest and besides there's a
aquí entre el pecho y aparte hay un
little one so that later they tell me the brunette that
solito para que luego me digan la morena
I'm getting fat and it's that it
que me estoy poniendo gordo y es que es
's true that for something although it's not
que es verdad que por algo aunque no es
because the holy spirit came and
porque ha venido el espíritu santo y me
planted a teat and a
ha plantado aquí una tetilla y una
tummy here on me it's not that I start eating you
barriguita no es que me pongo a comer
know and then I was coming from Huelva and I was
saben y entonces venía yo de huelva y
coming along the road for the rumor and one of
venía por el camino para el runrún y de
these times when you have a flash you know
estas veces que tienes un flash sabe
this phrase that I forgot one thing in
esta frase que se me olvida una cosa en
the video the last video that was uploaded
el vídeo el último vídeo que está subido
to my channel about that precisely on
a mi canal sobre que precisamente sobre
the subject of Sergio Ramirez we have a couple
el tema de sergio ramírez tenemos un par
more videos uploaded on the
de vídeos más subió en el canal
main channel what happens is that YouTube takes a while to
principal lo que pasa que youtube tarda
put it green so that Monetti if
en ponerlo en verde para que monetti si
such but well tomorrow or the day after I'll
tal pero bueno mañana o pasado ya lo
release it and what I came to talk about now
sacaré y de lo que vengo a hablar ahora
is tremendous that I was coming along the way
es tremendo eso venía por el camino
remembering and suddenly dude
acordándome y de repente macho se va
the light bulb goes on and I already know  I
encendido la bombilla y yo ya se me
forgot to comment this in the video dude it
olvidó comentar esto en el vídeo tío me
makes me really angry because now I'm
da mucho coraje porque yo ahora lo estoy
doing it on the main channel where I
haciendo en el canal principal el que me
'm writing down everything in
estoy apuntando todas las cosas en
notebooks not as such
cuadernos no como tal
again the script as such because I do
de nuevo el guión como tal porque a mí a
n't like scripts what I
mí no me gustan los guiones yo lo que
do is improvised but I do
hago es improvisada pero sí que me
write down all the little things here so I do
apunto aquí todas las cositas para que
n't forget them
no se me pasen
because my head is at seven in the
porque tengo la cabeza a las siete la
afternoon my mother always tells me
tarde siempre mi madre me lo dice
one day she's going to leave your head
cualquier día te va a dejar la cabeza en
high on the table on top of a
lo alto de la mesa en lo alto de un
bastion or whatever and it makes me really
baluarte o lo que sea y me da muchísimo
angry that I take and upload a video to the
coraje que yo coja suba un vídeo al
main channel already edited with its
canal principal ya editado con su
thumbnail and everything and when I'm at the
miniatura y todo y cuando estoy en el
premiere I crash I forget to
estreno me haga [__] se me olvida
comment on this I forget this joke I
comentar esto se me olvida este chiste
forgot it makes me really angry and it's
se me olvidaron se me da mucho coraje y
something that I even forgot to
es una cosa que se me olvidó incluso
write down here and if I didn't write it down here
apuntarle aquí y como no lo apunte aquí
supporting it I said it in the video and
apoyando la dije en el vídeo y es
the thing is quite relevant in the
bastante relevante la cosa en la
next one and it's awesome also the thing the
siguiente y manda güevos además la cosa
thing is the next one and it's awesome it's
la cosa es la siguiente y manda huevo es
a screenshot that was seen that I would
una captura de pantalla que se vio que
publish it  this is manuel ribeiro
la publicaría el tal es manuel ribeiro
if you haven't seen the video that I uploaded
si no habéis visto el vídeo que subí
before this
antes que éste
manuel [ __ ]
manuel [__]
now I'm going to tell you why he uploads this
ahora voy a decir porque sube esta
screenshot this screenshot in which he says
captura esta captura en la que dice
okay or that I should open the writer and he
bueno ya o que abriera al escribe y le
says you have the channel let's get an
dice vos tenés el canal consigamos un
older man and let's do a soap opera you
hombre mayor y hagamos una novela te
come to Argentina tomorrow or I'll go to
venís argentina mañana o voy yo a
Uruguay and we record like he caught you or
uruguay y grabamos como que te atrapó o
something like that super viral is that already or cabrera
algo así súper viral es que ya o cabrera
is that
es que
the magic the magic of the internet is you already
la magia la magia de internet eres tú ya
or cabrera all the ideas that you have are
o cabrera todas las ideas que tienes son
super viral whether they are for better or for
súper virales que sean para bien o para
worse but super viral like for example that
mal pero super virales como por ejemplo
shitty stab that exists with
la puñalada esa de [__] que existe con
pink watercolor that nobody believed
acuarela aquí rosa que no se la creía o
but well he had saying it's not
nadie pero bueno tuvo diciendo no es
real it's real perfect and cabrera man
real es real perfecto y la cabrera tío
how disgusting of boredom you know what
qué punto asco de hastío sabéis lo que
happens this screenshot is uploaded by the talent
pasa que esta captura la sube el talent
manuel from this account that you see here
manuel de esta cuenta que se ve aquí
above you know but the same thing is not the
arriba sabes pero lo mismo no es el
real one it's manuel I imagine that
verdadero es manuel yo me imagino que
this will be one of the dozens of accounts
esto será una de las decenas de cuentas
that came from emanuel and diego  cabrera
que salieron de emanuel y diego cabrera
del would write all and this friend
del escribiría todas y esta colega
public okay you have to be stupid you also
público vale hay que ser tonto también
have to be stupid because it turns out that they
hay que ser tonto por resulta ser que
upload this video from Sergio Ramirez's account
suben desde la cuenta de sergio ramírez
okay right now I'm going to
este videito vale ahora mismo yo me voy
subscribe to this channel and I want
a de suscribir de este canal y quiero
everyone to do the same okay don't
que todo el mundo haga lo mismo vale no
give him even a minimum not a minimum okay
le deis ni un mínimo ni un mínimo vale
of what they want okay 84 thousand dislikes I do
de lo que quieren vale 84 mil dislike yo
n't even know why he has likes
no sé ni siquiera porque tiene likes
okay I don't know why there are people who give him
vale yo no sé porque hay gente que le da
this I don't know if they are not
la ya esto no sé si es que no son
aware of what's going on but just
consciente de lo que está pasando pero
in case share this video with your
por si acaso compartir este vídeo con tu
kinski okay of that rate that they upload this
kinski vales de esa tasa que suben este
video with a man what a poor
vídeo con un señor que pobrecito este
man with everyone's shirt and endless
hombre con la camiseta de todos y sin
from there from the good plaza that they sell them
de ahí del bien plaza que las venden
down there still endlessly I have an air nike
abajo todavía sin fin tengo un air nike
and adidas everyone dresses how they want okay we're
y adidas cada uno viste como quiere vale
going to respect that the thing that
eso lo vamos a respetar la cosa que
was you this man is maybe
fuiste tú que este hombre lo mismo es
another bum that they caught like the
otro vagabundo que han cogido como el
king they gave him 20 payment take eat the
rey se le dieron 20 pago toma cómete la
toothpaste because coming from
pasta de dientes porque viniendo de la
cabrera I expect whatever ok or from
cabrera me espero lo que sea ok o de
friends talking  with you I do
amigos hablando con ustedes
n't want this happening with everything that
no quiero ocurriendo con todo lo que
happened but believe me it was very difficult to
pasó pero créame que fue muy difícil
record this video a lot of things happened
grabar este vídeo pasaron muchas cosas
for example like any unicanal
por ejemplo como que cualquiera unicanal
trusting many people I think I was
confíe en muchas personas creo que me
wrong to trust her I without realizing it I
equivoqué confiar en ella yo sin darme
allowed them to hurt me when
cuenta permití que me hagan daño cuando
I commented on the video of success I never thought it was
comenté el vídeo del éxito nunca pensé
going to have so much impact I
que iba a tener tanta repercusión yo
just wanted to travel and be able to meet him
sólo quería viajar y poder conocerlo
throw me he has a Uruguayan Argentine accent
echarme tiene acento uruguayo argentino
this man is not from Mexico or anything
este hombre no es de méxico ni de coña
this man from Cuernavaca is far away
este hombre de cuernavaca le pilla lejos
okay this man gets worse with the cow
vale este hombre empeora con a la vaca
but but but he doesn't live in Cuernavaca
pero pero pero no vive en cuernavaca
but with the rapid of my channel I lost his
pero con el rápido de mi canal perdí su
tip there is only
punta existe solo
[Music]
[Música]
one way to communicate with Luis
una una forma de comunicarme con luis
Aymat in all the forms attentive to the
aymat en todas las formas atentos a la
form the only way that exists to
forma a la única forma que existe de
communicate with Luisito company with
comunicarse con luisito empresa con la
which I could only contact him
cual solamente podría contactarme con él
and they do not respond to me that is why I
y no me responden por eso es que
need I am
necesito
going to leave a link in the description of
voy a dejar un link en la descripción de
ending the days and I need something to be
terminar los días y necesito que algo se
downloaded in that application is created or
baje en esa aplicación se cree o
needs that everyone goes in that
necesita que todos se van en esa
application
aplicación
and in case someone  have questions here you have
y por si alguien tiene dudas aquí tenéis
the link we give it and in the application is I don't
el link le damos y en la aplicación está
know what because it could applications it's
no sé qué porque podría aplicaciones
okay but if you notice now or
está vale pero si os fijáis ya o
cabrera help me contact or visited
cabrera ayúdenme a contactar o visitó
that cristina cabrera man how [ __ ] sad
que cristina cabrera tío que [__] triste
really I was already commenting on my
de verdad ya lo estuve comentando en mi
video that these are people that
vídeo que esto es gente que a mí me da
disgust me because they have broken all the magic
asco porque que han roto toda la magia
of a super beautiful thing that could have
de una cosa súper bonita que podía haber
happened and that is that luisito communicates and is going to
pasado y es que luisito comunica y va a
find an anonymous person thanks
encontrar a una persona anónima gracias
to the power of social networks the power
al poder de las redes sociales al poder
of the internet
de internet
a man who had simply released
un hombre que simplemente había soltado
there a comment with the sadness that he had not been
hay un comentario con la pena de que no
able to travel in his life a man
había podido viajar en la vida un hombre
there who must have written his comment and in
ahí que habrá escrito su comentario y de
good faith first the [ __ ] brat gets in
buena fe primero se mete el [__] niñato
is deleting the account and now the
esté quitando la cuenta y ahora ya el
mongol west already cabrera man they don't have I don't
mongol oeste ya cabrera tío no tienen no
know how many millions of subscribers man
sé cuántos millones de suscriptores tío
what need does he have to stick his [ __ ]
qué necesidad tiene de meter sus [__] y
dirty noses everywhere I go to
sucias narices en todas partes yo a
cabrera
cabrera
scum man you are a [ __ ] scum
escoria tío eres una putísima escoria
man your nose is not mine where they don't
tío no me está tu nariz ande no te
call you man I make a video commenting on a
llaman tío hago un vídeo comentando a un
video collaborating man you don't have millions
vídeo colaborando tío no tienes millones
of  subscribers well a video and if you
de suscriptores pues un vídeo y si te
want to get into the subject and scratch a
quieres meter en el tema y rascar una
visit like for example and it's me with my
visita como por ejemplo y soy yo con mi
last video and since we have done almost
último vídeo y como hemos hecho casi
all the channels to the CEO rocket and it must
todos los canales al ceo cohete y debe
be me I'm going to help you I'm going to travel to
ser yo voy a ayudar te voy a viajar a
Cuernavaca I'm going to look for you for an
cuernavaca voy a buscarte a una
investment but you are a dirty
inversión pero tú eres una sucia
negotiator knowing that this
tratativas cogido sabiendo que esta
person has the channel stolen because it is that they have
persona tiene el canal robado porque es
stolen the channel and surely
que han robado el canal y seguramente no
the complaint is not going to be taken because
se va a llevar la denuncia porque el
Mr. Ramirez will not even have found out what
señor ramírez ni se habrá enterado lo
has happened the man will surely
que ha pasado el hombre seguramente
have seen that he cannot enter the
habrá visto que no puede entrar la
account he has created another one of all by
cuenta se ha creado otra de todas por
ass he says he will be finding out about nothing the
culo dice estará enterando de nada el
illicit communication and he is talking about the
ilícito comunicación y está hablando el
subject because once that once he
tema porque ya una vez que ya una vez
started here to get involved let the
que ya empezó aquí a meterse deja que el
hacker uncle clown this supposed
hacker tío payaso este que el supuesto
hacker who takes the account from Luisito
hacker que la quita la cuenta a luisito
communicates this guy takes it and from the first
comunica este tío coge y desde el primer
video that he uploaded he already put a
vídeo que subió ya puso un link
monetized link in his in the description of the
monetizado en su en la descripción del
video with his channel uncle trying to make a
vídeo con su canal tío intentando sacar
profit from wherever uncle and that's what I'm
lucro de donde sea tío y es lo que os
telling you okay you can make a profit
digo vale se puede sacar lucro
by increasing the dissemination of the news that
aumentando difundiendo las noticias que
is something fun that has the  people not
sea algo divertido que tenga la gente no
here we are with the mystery as a
aquí estamos con el misterio como un
case as a case of entertainment
caso como un caso de entretenimiento
like a series but it's [ __ ] up all the
como una serie pero está [__] toda la
magic man it's that he has [ __ ] up all the magic
magia tío es que ha [__] toda la magia
a 60 year old man who surely lives
un señor de 60 años que seguramente viva
in a country that is quite humble or
en un país que sea bastante humilde o lo
whatever not in a small town if I'm not
que sea no en un pueblecito si no me
mistaken that has not had the opportunity
equivoco que no he tenido la oportunidad
to travel in his life and now finally
de viajar en su vida y ahora por fin
thanks to luisito comunica he was going to
gracias a luisito comunica la iba a
have it finally he was going to have the opportunity
tener por fin iba a tener la oportunidad
that he wanted so much and to know put two
que tanto deseaba y saber metido dos
lines in the middle to scrape together four
líneas por medio para rascar cuatro
miserable bucks because the truth is every
duros miserable porque la verdad yo cada
time I upload a video talking about some
vez que subió vídeo hablando sobre algún
salsa or Mexican or Uruguayan who
salse o mexicano o uruguayo que
precisely ordered the video to be uploaded
precisamente mandó subir el vídeo
laughing that they hit you already cabrera
riéndome de que te pegaron ya cabrera
is when they hit me what did you give
está cuando te pegaron a mí que le diste
there's a little bite to the curb the rope
hay un bocadito al bordillo la cuerda
you know the whole point of elche the saying
sabéis todo el punto de elche el dicho
of canton since he fell and bit
de cantón ya que se cayó y mordió a la
life from dallas without meaning to well I
vida de dallas sin querer pues yo a
fell to cabrera and with a curb
cabrera se se cayó y con un bordillo
look I'm going to put it in fact let's go here I
mira lo voy a poner de hecho vamos aquí
already had it cabrera with the
lo tenía ya cabrera con la camiseta de
viral shirt okay already
viral vale ya
I  it would be a pain to wear my
ya me jodería ponerme yo para salir de
own t-shirt out to party today imagine and he
fiesta la propia camiseta hoy imagina y
gave me over there with the
me dio por ahí con la camiseta de
ravioli flange t-shirt I'm
ravioli brida
not going to see evidence
no voy a ver evidencia
[Music]
[Música]
and look I
y mira
hit him he falls place he hits him and falls you hit him
le pegue se cae sitio le pega y se cae
but how could you how could you think of
le pegues pero cómo se te ocurre cómo se
going stop stop that guy 11
te ocurre irte para para ese macho 11
but wait here comes the good part
pero esperan aquí viene la parte bonita
although the good part is worth look with those he
si bien la parte bonita vales mira con
comes already or around here he had
las que viene ya o por aquí ha
breakfast sometimes there's a pot of salt
desayunado a veces hay una olla de sal
a motorcycle plus a curb and take weapons
una moto más un bordillo y tome armas
but in order to lose here he comes already or half
pero ante perder aquí viene ya o media
running poses so they're
corriendo posturitas para que le están
hitting him hold on everywhere he had a
pegando aguanta por todos lados ha
shitty breakfast he has a little toast I
desayunado [__] tiene una tostadita
don't vote anymore with butter and the sauce
no voto más con manteca y los salseado
of these people monetize [ __ ] I shot
de esta gente monetizan una [__] tiro
and to take 4 out of 14 us burst the
y por llevarte 4 de 14 us reventado la
true magic of au cabrera then
magia de verdad de au cabrera luego no
you don't complain that they are some guys more
te quejas de que sean unos tíos más
hated and understand why is it that we can't
odiado y entender por qué es que no te
give you the opportunity because
podemos dar la oportunidad porque es que
everything you do is [ __ ] mind the same
todo lo que haces es [__] mente igual
fake stab you get a girlfriend to
puñalada falsa te echas una novia para
throw her face down in a thong on the bed and
echarla boca abajo en tanga en la cama y
spray her with an instinct you start
rociarla con un instinto te pones a
threatening a 15 year old boy
amenazar a un chaval de 15 años
stealing his instagram account stealing his
robándole la cuenta de instagram robando
twitter account
la cuenta de twitter
well it wasn't going well now copying
pues no te iba ahora bien copiando a
logan paula making yourself a house in a
logan paula haciéndote una casa en una
mansion with a few from youtube who
mansión con unos cuantos de youtube que
even had her own dwarf with you don't get involved
incluso tenía su propio enano contigo no
in other people's stories guys
te meta en las historias de los demás a
that you and luisito communicate look
tíos que tú a luisito comunicas mira
luisito communicates up to here and I that it
luisito comunica hasta aquí y yo que
opens up to yago yao get up from the floor
abre hasta yago yao levantarte del suelo
to the curb and nothing guys you only
de al bordillo y nada chavales solamente
wanted this video to warn okay so that
querías este vídeo para avisar vale para
more people don't fall for this guy
que más gente no caiga en que este señor
is serious ramirez already forgotten about sergio
es serio ramírez olvidado ya de sergio
ramirez okay the magic I give up for
ramírez vale la magia yo la doy por
lost I don't know if there is a minimal
perdida no sé si existirá una mínima
possibility they said out there that there was
posibilidad decían por ahí que había
another account sergio ramirez silva it wouldn't
otra cuenta sergio ramírez silva no
be like that it would be true yes it would be a lie
sería así será verdad sí será mentira no
I don't know if there is some way in which
lo sé yo si se ocurre alguna forma de la
I can help okay you have my
que yo pueda ayudar vale tenéis aquí mi
channel here you have my word and my
canal tenéis aquí mi palabra y mi
trust here okay I'm not going to be  so
confianza vale que yo no voy a ser tan
fake okay if anyone knows the
falso vale si alguien conoce al
real 6 ramirez can you contact
verdadero 6 ramírez podéis contactar
me I'm just to ask for whatever
conmigo yo sólo para solicito lo que sea
okay but these things but his guys are
vale pero estas cosas pero sus tíos
pathetic because it's been scratching however you
penoso porque es que ha sido rascar como
know the streets anyway
sea ya sabes las calles como sea ya se
the issue is over Mr. Ramirez but we're
ha acabado el tema señor ramírez pero
going to put a link here to an
vamos a meter aquí un link de una
application that charged per click okay
aplicación que cobró por clic vale
because this guy charges per download per
porque este señor cobra por descarga por
client for whatever go [ __ ] yourself
client por lo que sea vete a tomar por
already cabrera man we're on the
culo ya cabrera tío que estamos en
internet fed up with you and I'm not
internet hasta la [__] de ti y no te
going to wish that you 7 on the channel that
voy a desear que te 7 en el canal que
the serranos both the channel is that
los serranos a los dos el canal es que
I know how bad it is it doesn't have to
me sé lo mal que se pasa no tiene que
be that but you or change girl or
sea eso pero ti o cambiar chica o
cabrera change the place until the next
cabrera cambia el sitio hasta el próximo
video people
vídeo gente